http://www.jncs.com/php2/showinfo.php?id=privacy

Optional Discreet Graphics
Intel Gen 10!
Asus Z490-A, i7-10700K
8 Cores, 16GB
500GB PCIe 4.0 SSD
$1,482
New-Small & Powerful!
i3-10100 to i9-10900
Up to 64GB, 2TB SSD
Win 10 or 10 Pro
J&N Computer Services, Inc.
Established 1994
JNCS now includes AMD® Ryzen® 5000 Series CPU options for X570 and B550 Systems!
Home & Specials
Servers
Servers by Chassis (1U, 2U)
NUC10i7FNK - Intel® i7
Intel NUC - 9th Generation (Ghost Canyon) High-End Desktop Replacement
Custom by CPU Type
Intel Core i3/i5/i7/i9 10th Gen (Socket 1200)
Mini-ITX
Micro ATX (MATX)
Ordering Instructions
Warranty/Returns - Important - Please Read Before Purchasing
Ebay Feedback for JNCS
.
JNCS Privacy Statement
J&N Computer Services (JNCS) is a privately owned company based in Fairport, NY. What follows is JNCS's online privacy policy, which governs personal information gathered on our Internet sites.
JNCS’s Commitment to Online Security
Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. JNCS encrypts billing information wherever JNCS requests it. All JNCS employees and contractors with access to personal information obtained on the JNCS web site are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with JNCS. JNCS does not allow on-line access to any personal customer information.
Personal Information that JNCS May Collect Online
JNCS collects personal and business information online, including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, and billing information.
JNCS does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of our site is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.
How JNCS Uses Personal Information Collected Online
Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted,
such as to reply to your emails, send confirmation invoices and shipping notifications, and process billing and
business requests. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you
may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about specials offered by JNCS. This election box
only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or
remove your name from a JNCS list by contacting us at (855) 333-3482.
Information will Not Be Shared
We never sell or rent your personal information.
In order to charge your credit card for the amount of your purchase, your credit card number and name will be transmitted to the bank we use for credit card clearing.
JNCS may also release personal information under the following circumstances:
Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
Where our records indicate a purchaser may have engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
To appropriate government agencies, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.
Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please call us toll-free at (855) 333-3482 with the new information.
Computer Tracking and Cookies
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public. It is not provided to others. We may use third-party tracking solutions that collect data for the sole purpose of web site traffic analysis.
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. JNCS uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information and are used solely as a way to enable you to navigate our site and purchase items securely.
Problems or Complaints with JNCS Privacy Policy
If you have an issue about JNCS compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us locally at (585) 388-8780 or toll-free at (855) 333-3482.
revised July 1, 2004
Contents Copyright©1995-2020J&N Computer Services, Inc.
